[opening theme music playing]
GOTTA BUY A STEP STOOL
Here's pepper spray.
You just aim it at their face and try
to get as much as you can in their eyes.
Okay? Definitely stings.
[Haru laughs] All right.
This is a really loud siren.
You want the sound to reach
as far as possible.
So it's modeled after a wolf howl, huh?
- [siren chirps]
- [exclaims, groans]
[Haru chuckles]
And the star of the show
is this little stun gun, ah?
Let's see here.
I was told this will take down
anything that gets in your way.
- [stun gun crackling]
- [exclaims]
Yeah. I think it's sweet
you're so protective.
But isn't this a bit much?
Here's the thing.
I have a feeling Melon's
not done with you yet.
I'm not always gonna be
by your side to protect you.
I know how to take care of myself,
you know.
You're not hearing me.
If we were dealing with just some teacher,
that'd be fine.
But this is a killer with a grudge
against mixed couples.
And he's definitely got some
anger issues with his parents.
He's a serial devourer
and boss of the Shishi-Gumi--
He's the crazy guy who put
a few bullets in you. I get it.
Uh... Well, it's not about me.
This is about you.
You didn't tell me anything
about what happened at school.
And also, um...
And also what?
It's just that...
No, never mind.
It's nothing.
Nothing?
You won't get mad?
I don't know.
[hesitatingly] Well...
You and Melon, uh... Did...
You didn't like him, right?
Maybe just a little?
- Huh?
- Uh...
I mean, one day, I remember
you had Melon's scent on you.
And even though you said
he was really shady,
you still made that promise with him,
so I was--
Legoshi!
That does make me mad!
The only person
I'm interested in being with is you.
Huh?
- [chuckles]
- [scoffs] Really?
- I'm glad this is so hilarious to you.
- [thuds]
Hey, there.
- Hmm?
- Degoshi.
So here's some bad news.
You're suspected of murder.
- Huh?
- What? Murder?
They're about to put you on a wanted list.
It'll be all over the news.
You know, the tattoo parlor thing?
"The tattoo parlor thing"?
You've got it wrong.
They were already dead when I got there.
What am I missing?
Well, the police want
to bust your hide ASAP.
People get scared with stuff like this.
As soon as your name drops,
here comes the press.
Your story is gonna be
a popular search online.
And unfortunately,
it won't matter if it's true or not.
Well, I'm sure Mr. Yahya would underst--
Understand?
Are you sure about that?
Mm. Well, maybe not with that tone.
- You have devouring on your record, right?
- Huh?
If it were me on probation,
I'd steer clear of trouble.
Wait a minute.
How do you know all of this?
[Corn] I'm Intel Chief
of The 500 Cornered Rats.
But at the end of the day,
you either listen or you don't.
All right.
If you're ever in a bind,
just give me a call.
You can try hiding,
but they will find you.
Also, if you think you're
laying low, you're not.
RATS
[Haru] He seems serious.
What are you thinking about?
I don't have time to get arrested.
Melon's still on the loose.
[sighs] Is this even real?
So does that mean you were
at the crime scene then?
Geez. Why did you even
go to that tattoo parlor?
The last thing you'd do is get a tattoo.
Well, it's Melon's go to studio, though.
I thought it was a slam dunk.
I needed a lead and I thought I'd get it
from those tattoo guys.
Hmm. That sounds--
Uh, don't worry. Hold on.
I didn't do anything dangerous.
[sighs] You know what?
My school may have what you need.
Huh?
A lead on Melon or Professor Lumrong.
Something might turn up.
You're right!
- Let's go!
- Wait! Ah!
Hang on. Hang on.
- I'll go ask around.
- Huh?
[Haru chuckles]
Hey, you'd stand out like a sore thumb.
Hmm?
Uh, did you hear me?
[Legoshi] Hmm.
Legoshi?
You know...
you're at a perfectly
kissable height right now.
[Haru gasps]
It just feels like...
kissing you would be so natural
in this moment.
I mean... now?
I... I guess that's fine.
[whimsical music playing]
[Haru sighs]
Do you mind if we put this on hold?
- On hold?
- [sighs]
Here's the thing.
Once I catch Melon,
the Beastar is going to clear my record
of a devouring incident.
[Haru] What?
Then you and I won't have any problem
being together, officially.
So maybe we put it on hold for now.
- [chuckles]
- [Haru grumbles]
Oh, I get it.
On hold.
Aren't we a little full of ourselves?
Haru? Wait, what did I say?
Oh, nothing.
[Legoshi] Come on!
Haru!
UDON BEBEBE
We have reason to believe that the victim
got deliveries from your restaurant.
Yeah. Something wrong with that?
And he ordered from you often?
Yep. I usually leave
all the delivery stuff to Legoshi.
Did you find the various wounds
to his face or arms unusual?
Well, the kid is a young wolf.
A few scrapes really that big a deal?
So you're saying that's normal?
[stutters]
Oh, that's not what I meant by that.
[Seven] Legoshi was always really nice.
Just a normal kid to me.
I guess you haven't heard
about his record of devouring?
No, I never heard anything about that.
[gasps] But when I think about it,
he always seemed very mindful.
Like, careful never to touch an herbivore.
Hmm. Why do you think that is?
I guess he just cared about
putting everyone's mind at ease.
In other words, there was a possibility
he could hurt someone?
I don't think so.
I haven't seen signs
of anything like that lately.
So no recent examples
but that wasn't always the case?
[sighs] Was he satisfying his hunger
with devourings?
[suspenseful music playing]
[Louis] Legoshi. He got set up again.
LEGOSHI WANTED AS MURDER SUSPECT
My guess is
Melon's misdirecting the police
so he can take down his next victim.
What do I do?
[Peach] This was the Live Together
promotion office.
[giggles] If you want to support us
and help stop prejudice
against interspecies romance for good,
just make sure you like and subscribe.
Liv Together!
- [beep]
- [cattle] And cut.
- How was that?
- Good.
I think this one's gonna get some likes.
- Hopefully we can top 30.
- Yeah, no doubt.
[Louis] Excuse me.
Whoa! Louis!
Sorry to interrupt you all.
Oh! Oh! Let me guess.
You want to help with our mission, right?
Uh... Yeah, maybe later.
It's more about this string
of recent devourings.
They seem to be aimed
at interspecies couples.
The killer is very dangerous,
and he hasn't been caught yet.
But I think you can help.
Are you up for making a self-defense video
and posting it to your channel?
Basically telling people
to watch their backs.
Is that a good idea?
I certainly understand your concerns.
But I don't want anyone else
to get caught up in these murders.
You guys have a large following, right?
Your videos get a lot of views.
I think you could do some good.
- Well, what do you think?
- [bull] Mm.
Well, since you're famous,
could we just use your name?
You want to use my name?
[cell phone buzzing]
Huh?
Excuse me.
This is Louis.
[Mayor on phone]
Listen, where are you right now?
I'm at school. Why?
Do you see any press around?
- Any police?
- What?
I've been following the news
about your friend, the wanted one.
I've pulled a few strings,
so the investigation steers clear of you.
I don't know what you mean by that.
If it got out that the wolf
is your best friend,
and on top of that,
you let that friend eat your leg?
Guessing I don't have to tell you
what a problem that would be for us.
For the time being,
don't do any press, no interviews.
Stay out of sight and behave yourself.
Got it?
[line disconnects]
[sighs wearily]
So what do you think about our offer?
You can go ahead and use my name.
Yes! All right!
[Bill] Nice to come together.
- [Kibi] Yeah!
- [Bill] Nice.
[Els] I think we're doing
pretty great so far.
- [Kibi] You know it.
- [Bill] Everyone is doing great.
Doesn't it feel like Juno and Pena
are doing a lot better?
Totally. Who would have thought
they'd mesh so well?
Yeah, those two were definitely
a challenge for us.
- [Els chuckles]
- What? [gasps]
[Els and Kibi gasp]
DEVOURING CLUB
GO TO HELL
This is terrible.
It has to do with Legoshi, I think.
He's not even a club member anymore.
We didn't do anything
to deserve this kind of bullying.
Unbelievable!
Only cowards do this.
Uh, to be fair,
don't you all remember when we had to deal
with that devouring incident with Tim?
And then there was Louis who got his leg
eaten so he could capture Riz.
- Huh?
- Uh, we've had some drama in the club.
Are you trying to put this on the seniors?
- That's not what I meant.
- [growls]
[herbivores stammer]
Well, now we all know what we have to do.
We're amazing when we work together.
When us carnivores
and herbivores work as a team,
we can show whoever did this nonsense
they made a big mistake.
- You're so cool.
- Yeah.
[Bill] Still, I don't know what to believe
with this news about Legoshi.
[guard] Professor Lumrong?
[Haru] Yeah, he left in
the middle of the semester, so...
You don't know where he went
to work next, do you?
I'd say forget about that.
I went through his resume
and it was nothing but lies.
Not a single thing on there matched up.
So no contact info I bet?
Just more lies.
If you ask me,
they need thorough background checks.
If you don't know
who you're really hiring,
how is anyone supposed to feel safe?
[sighs] Yeah.
Thanks for all your help.
[Haru grunts]
[sighs]
Maybe the academic office knows something.
- [rustling]
- Huh?
[rustling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[whimpers softly]
[sighing wearily]
Oh, it's you.
You're the one that
used to hang around Gohin.
Yeah. You're the bamboo shop lady.
Tell me how it feels
being so famous and such.
Huh?
All the reporters
are saying you're wanted.
What? They're saying that I'm wanted?
Yeah.
Huh. Here I thought you were
so young and carefree.
Well, I just, uh... Yeah.
- Excuse me.
- Huh?
[Legoshi] I can't go to Gohin.
He doesn't deserve that.
RATS
[sighs] I guess I'll give it a shot.
Hmm.
[sighs softly]
RATS
[water trickling]
You're here.
Seems like everything you said came true.
I am definitely on the Most Wanted List.
This had to have been
part of Melon's trap.
A trap, huh?
Well, I went over to the tattoo parlor
when I was trying to find Melon.
There were two dead bodies inside
and the police were instantly there.
I see.
[stomach growling]
Oh. Uh...
[laughs sheepishly]
You're hungry, I guess.
Huh?
We have some meat for you to eat.
No, thanks. I don't eat meat, actually.
Don't be so picky.
No, it's not about that.
Just eat it then.
You don't know when
you'll eat again, Degoshi.
Huh? My name's not Degoshi. It's Legoshi.
Fugitives need to use an alias.
That's like the same name.
If you won't eat it, I will.
Hey, stop! Stop, stop, stop! No fair!
Give it back to me!
Do you guys really need to fight?
I'm sure there's plenty of meat
around in the black market.
Degoshi, meat is expensive.
We can't always afford it.
- Really?
- Remember this.
The meat lined up in those stores
is reserved for business.
Carnivores from mainstream society
will buy it, no matter what the price is.
And the prices just keep rising.
- Give it!
- [ICorn] Most carnivores
living in the black market
don't have that kind of money.
That's why we the 500 cornered rats,
were taking money from slime merchants
and distributing it to everyone.
You like that?
So that's why Mr. Corne
is cooperating with Mr. Yahya.
Cooperating?
Not exactly.
Corne is nothing more
than a lapdog for the police.
That sounds sort of insulting to dogs.
I say Yahya is the devil.
And I can't stand that
they're working together.
Outside the walls,
those guys only make rules for themselves,
and carnivores get zero freedom.
You think I'm wrong about that?
Uh... Well...
So carnivores come
to the black market to buy meat,
and that way everyone's happy.
Uh, yeah, I guess.
Degoshi, didn't they frame you
for something that's not your fault?
You can't trust creatures
who would do that to ya.
The only good thing about herbivores
is how delicious their meat tastes.
[both] So yummy!
[Corn] All right. Time for bed.
[both] Bedtime!
[Legoshi] Hmm.
Never in my 18 years would I think
I'd find myself in a place like this.
CELEBRATING YOUR AWARD
CONGRATS ON THE GRAND PRIZE
[inhales]
[exhales]
- [cell phone ringing]
- Hmm?
Oh. The chairman?
OGMA
Nepetalactol.
You figured out its molecular structure.
The active compound found in catnip.
And you synthesized it?
Fantastic.
I appreciate you saying that, sir.
Applying this to feline attractants,
this could be revolutionary.
It seems you're quite gifted.
Which brings me to my request.
We're having a production issue
with a certain project.
There's a stability problem.
This looks like some kind of
nutritional supplement?
We're experimenting with artificial meat.
Oh, I see.
I'd like you to work closely with
Ogura Foods on its development.
With Ogura Foods?
Ah! Because Louis is going to marry...
I mean...
I'm not good
at, uh, collaborative research.
We'll provide the necessary funding.
Consider it a blank check.
In addition, we'll prepare a private lab
solely for your use.
This is the executive key.
You're welcome to it any day, anytime.
Hmm.
You're not impressed.
Very well.
We'll throw in lounge access, too.
[chuckles]
Well, that sounds nice.
Our delivery expectation
is by the third quarter.
Yes, sir.
If I may, uh,
about the artificial meat project,
where are we in terms of its development?
Don't hover above your pay grade.
Uh... Yes, sir.
It'll be our trump card
for the Zoolympic bid.
We need this done well and on time.
I'll be sure and give it my best.
Thank you, sir.
Arranged marriages,
since you mentioned it,
are an effective means
of bringing us together and forging
rather important political alliances.
[sighs]
Well, I'm certainly no expert, sir,
but when it comes to procreation,
the amount of testosterone that's produced
by the male is an important factor.
Excuse me, sir.
[door closes echoes]
[reporter speaking on radio]
[reporter] ...an employee and a customer
were found in the scene
inside the second-generation
Seiryu Tattoo Studio
in the First Ocean District.
Police discovered a large quantity
of the recently banned energy drink Kines
in the apartment
of the suspected wolf at large Legoshi.
- What?
- Any information regarding...
There's no way they found that in my room.
[man 1] Empty Kenis cans were also found
at the scene of the interspecies
murder cases, weren't they?
[man 2] Yes, it's natural to think that
the unsolved serial-devouring incidents
may be related.
It's possible Legoshi
was also behind these crimes.
[man 1] So what's his motive here?
[man 2] Well, making carnivores drink
Kenis is to get them to kill herbivores,
then killing those attacking carnivores?
What a heinous beast, if you ask me.
- [man 1] If we don't catch him soon...
- [man 2] ...then his killing spree
- will continue.
- [man 1] Right.
[man 2] The faster we find
this deadly gray wolf, the better.
[reporter]
We appreciate your input, gentlemen.
Next up is the weather forecast.
[sighs] This is such a mess.
Degoshi, congratulations.
You're the most dangerous carnivore
in the whole world.
There's nothing funny about this.
Seriously.
Well, it looks like you'll have to hide
out here until the heat dies down.
[Legoshi sighs]
[Legoshi] I wonder if Haru is all right.
- [girl] Haru!
- Huh?
Tell me you've seen this.
Is this true?
LEGOSHI WANTED FOR MURDER
- No. Don't believe everything you read.
- So scary. Are you okay, Haru?
This is even worse than Ako's boyfriend.
Well, he said it's a false accusation.
Wait. So, like, you believe
what your boyfriend says?
That's true love. [laughs]
What are you thinking?
Well, I just have this feeling
like someone's watching me.
Uh-oh. Maybe it's your boyfriend.
But wait, aren't you the one who's always
saying you can protect yourself?
[Haru]
After 19 years as a rabbit, I get it.
No matter how much I act tough
about protecting myself,
if someone stands behind me, it's scary,
because I know I could never win.
[tense music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[Haru breathing shakily]
[footsteps approaching, stops]
Uh...
[footsteps continue approaching]
[panting]
[footsteps stop]
[Haru grunts]
- [stun gun crackling]
- [groaning]
[Haru panting]
[groaning]
[closing theme song playing]